Environmental Advocates of New York; Records apap104
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Issues, 1930-2004; 1; 58.4 cubic ft.
  - Solid Waste Management, 1974-1995; 1.12; 8.0 cubic ft.
    - Incineration, Department of Environmental Conservation, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Incineration, Dioxin Emissions, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Incineration, Dioxin Emissions, 1985 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Incineration, Dioxin Emissions, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Incineration, Dioxin Emissions, Undated (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Incineration, Environmental Planning Lobby, Reports, 1985 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Incineration, Environmental Quality Bond Act of 1972, 1985 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Incineration, Europe, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Incineration, Facilities, Albany, 1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Incineration, Federal, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Incineration, Funding, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Incineration, General Information, 1981-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Incineration, General Information, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Incineration, General Information, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Incineration, Health Effects, 1985-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Incineration, Incineration vs. Recycling Analysis, 1984-1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Incineration, Municipal Incineration, 1987-1992 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Incineration, New Clippings, 1979-1985 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Incineration, News Clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Incineration, News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Incineration, New York State Hospitals, 1985-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Incineration, Other States, California, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Incineration, Other States, California, 1985-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Incineration, Other States, Connecticut, 1977; 1984-1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Incineration, Other States, Florida, 1981; 1984-1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Incineration, Other States, Illinois, 1984; 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Incineration, Other States, Massachusetts, 1975; 1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Incineration, Other States, Michigan, 1985; 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Incineration, Other States, New Jersey, 1984-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Incineration, Other States, Ohio, 1979-1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Incineration, Other States, Oregon, 1981 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Incineration, Other States, Pennsylvania, Undated (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Incineration, Other States, Rhode Island, 1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Incineration, Other States, Vermont, 1981-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Incineration, Other States, Virginia, 1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Incineration, Procurement, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Incineration, Publications, 1986-1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Incineration, Regional, Broome County, 1984-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Incineration, Regional, Capital District, 1985-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Incineration, Regional, Cattaraugus County, 1983-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Incineration, Regional, Dutchess County, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Incineration, Regional, Finger Lakes, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Incineration, Regional, Hempstead, 1979-1980; 1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Incineration, Regional, Hudson Falls, 1985-1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Incineration, Regional, Long Island, 1983-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Incineration, Regional, Moreau, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Incineration, Regional, New York City, 1981-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Incineration, Regional, Niagara, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Incineration, Regional, Oneida, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Incineration, Regional, Onondaga, 1983; 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Incineration, Regional, Ontario, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Incineration, Regional, Peekskill, 1982-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Incineration, Regional, Port Washington, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Incineration, Regional, Poughkeepsie, 1983-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Incineration, Regional, Rochester, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Incineration, Regional, Rockland County, Undated (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Incineration, Regional, Saratoga County, 1985-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Incineration, Regional, Schoharie, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Incineration, Regional, Syracuse, 1983-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 36)
    - Incineration, Regional, Ulster County, 1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 37)
    - Incineration, Regulations, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 38)
    - Incineration, Reports, 1975-1983 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 39)
    - Incineration, Reports, 1984 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 40)
    - Incineration, Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 41)
    - Incineration, Report, "The Financial and Environmental Impact of Garbage Incineration", Undated (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 42)
    - Incineration, St. Lawrence County, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 43)
    - Incineration, Signal, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 44)
    - Incineration, Siting, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 45)
    - Incineration, Standards, 1984-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 46)
    - Incineration, Technical, 1982-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 47)
    - Incinerator Ash, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 48)
    - Infectious Wastes, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Issues, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Landfills, 1991-1992 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Landfills, General Information, 1983; 1986-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Legislation, 1985-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Legislation, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Low Cost Energy/Economic Development, 1993-1994 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Municipal Solid Waste, 1984-1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Municipal Solid Waste, Incineration, 1984-1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - News Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - New York Code Rules and Regulations, Part 36, Solid Waste Management Facilities, Volume 1, Draft, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - New York State Energy Plan, 1994 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - New York State Plan, 1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan, 1991-1992 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan, 1993-1994 Update (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - New York State Waste Reduction Council, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - New York State Waste Reduction Guidance Manual, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Office of Recycling Market Development, 1993-1994 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Office of Recycling Market Development, 1995 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Pollution Prevention/Economics, 1995 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Proceedings, 1987; 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Proceedings, 1990-1992 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Procurement, 1983; 1986 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Recycling, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Recycling, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Recycling, Advisory Group, 1979; 1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Recycling, Business, 1995 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Recycling, Case Studies, 1974; 1984-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Recycling, Composition Studies, 1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Recycling, Composting, 1983; 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Recycling, Department of Environmental Conservation, 1978; 1984-1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Recycling, Enhance Local Employment Creation Through Recycling Act, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Recycling, Environmental Impact, 1973; 1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 36)
    - Recycling, Flow Control, 1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 37)
    - Recycling Forum, 1985-1986 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 38)
    - Recycling, Industrial Recycling Program, 1978-1982 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 39)
    - Recycling, Industrial Recycling Program, 1983-1985 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Recycling, Legislation, 1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Recycling, Market Development, 1973; 1983-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Recycling, Market Development, 1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Recycling, Miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Recycling, New York City Recycling Bill, 1983; 1986-1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Recycling, New York City Recycling Bill, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Recycling, New York City Recycling Bill, 1991-1992; 1995 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Recycling, New York State Local Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Recycling, Paper, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Recycling, Plastics and Cans, 1985-1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Recycling, Plastics, 1985-1989 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Recycling, "Reclaiming Our Waste", Conference, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Recycling, "Recycle First" Campaign, 1971; 1992 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Recycling, Regional, Broome County, 1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Recycling, Regional, California, 1982-1985 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Recycling, Regional, New Jersey, 1982-1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Recycling, Regional, New York City, 1979; 1984-1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Recycling, Regional, Ulster County, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Recycling, Reports, 1978; 1985 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Recycling, Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Recycling, Tires, 1986; 1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Recycling, Waste Reduction, Packaging, 1982-1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Recycling, Waste Reduction, Work on Waste, 1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Recycling, World Watch Paper 76, 1987 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Regulations, 1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1986; 1993-1995 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Resource Recovery Testimony, 1979-1980 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Resource Recovery Testimony, 1983-1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Response to SEQR Comments on the Draft Supplement to the Generic Environmental Impact Statement/ Solid Waste Management Plan for the ANSWERS Watershed Planning Unit, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Sixth Annual Recycling Conference, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Solid Waste Issues, 1993-1995 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Solid Waste Management, New York, Master Plan Update, 1991 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Solid Waste Management Plan Annual Update Comments, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Solid Waste Management Plan, vol. 1, 1992 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Solid Waste Management Plan, vol. 2, 1992 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Solid Waste Penalties, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Solid Waste Policy Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), General Information, 1976-1979 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), General Information, 1980 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), General Information, 1981-1983 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), General Information, 1985-1988 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), General Information, 1985-1992 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), Undated (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), General Information, Undated (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), Handbook, 1991 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), Revisions, 1987 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - State Environmental Quality Review Act (SEQR), Revisions, 1988 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - State Plans, 1984-1986 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - State Plans, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Summary of Major Developments in Solid Waste Management In New York State, 1992 January-September (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Testimony, 1990; 1993-1994 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - "Update on Diapers", 1990 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Waste Reduction, 1994 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Waste Reduction and Packaging, 1991 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Waste Reduction Task Force, 1993 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan, Update, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management, Appendices, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan Responsiveness Survey, 1991 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
  - Tobacco, 1988-1997; 1.13; 0.4 cubic ft.
    The Tobacco subseries includes material related to the tobacco excise tax and smoking commission.
    - Legislation, 1989-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Tobacco Ban, Governor's Bill, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Tobacco Excise Tax, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Tobacco Excise Tax, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Tobacco Tax and Health Fund, 1988-1997 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Smoking Commission, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Smoking Commission, Smoking Task Force, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Smoking Commission, Smoking Task Force, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
  - Transportation, 1971-1996; 1.14; 2.0 cubic ft.
    The subseries Transportation contains correspondence, memorandums, news clippings, reports, statistics, and testimony related to the Westway (Long Island) project, air pollution, and Hudson River development. Related to this subseries is the material found in the Projects subseries in Series 4: Loretta Simon.
    - 21st Century Mobility, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Air Pollution, 1985; 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Air Pollution, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Battery Park City Authority, News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Cities and Population Statistics, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Coro Report, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Coro Report, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Crisis Program, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Electric Vehicles, 1990-1996 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Emissions Standards, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Enhancement Program, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Federal Legislation, 1982 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Gas Tax, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Hudson River Center, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Hudson River Development, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Hudson River Development, Hudson River Habitat Protection Bill, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - ICONN-Erie, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Infrastructure Bond Act of 1983, 1980-1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Intermodal Statewide Transportation Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Internal Memoranda, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Land Use, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Land Use and Transportation, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Memoranda and Notes, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Metropolitan Transportation Authority, 1988; 1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Metropolitan Transportation Authority, 1991; 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - News Releases, State of New York Executive Chamber, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - New York State Counties and Demographics, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Noise Control Act, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Policy, California, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Policy, Maine, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Policy, New Jersey, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Policy, Oregon, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Public Transportation, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Reports and Background Information, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Reports and Background Information, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 36)
    - Reports and Background Information, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 37)
    - Scoping Process, 1984; 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 38)
    - State Transportation Plan, 1986; 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 39)
    - State Transportation Plan, 1990; 1992-1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Testimony, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Transfer Development Rights, 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Transit, 1985; 1988-1990 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Tug Hill Commission, General, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Westway, 1977-1982 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Westway, 1983 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Westway, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Westway, 1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Westway, 1986-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Westway, Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Westway, Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Westway, Son of Westway, 1971; 1985-1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Westway, Son of Westway, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Westway, West Side Task Force, 1977-1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Westway, West Side Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Citizens Rapid Transit Committee, Buffalo, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Fixed Guideway Transit Investigation Survivory Report, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
  - Water, 1930-1995; 1.15; 7.0 cubic ft.
    The Water subseries includes material related to the Safe State Drinking Water Act (SSDRA), Clean Water Act, Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Hudson River - Westway (Long Island), State Safe Drinking Water Act (SSDWA), Proposition 65, Long Island Sound Study (LISS), lakes, rivers, oceans, reservoirs, and groundwater. The subseries' inclusive dates are 1930-1990 with the bulk of the subseries covering the period 1977-1989.
    - Articles, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Clean Water, Boehlert, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Clean Water, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Clean Water, Legislation, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Clean Water, Marina Pumpout, General Information, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Clean Water, Moynihan, Daniel, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Clean Water Act, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Clean Water Act, 1983-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Clean Water Act, General Information, 1971-1973; 1979-1981 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Clean Water Act, General Information, 1985; 1989; 1997 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Clean Water Network, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - County Water Quality Coordinating Committees for New York State, Directory, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Drinking Water Filtration, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Fluoridation, General Information, 1978-1981; 1988; 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Funding, Great Lakes, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Funding, Hudson, River, 1980-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Funding, Onondaga Lake, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Great Lakes, 1966; 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Great Lakes, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)